Othniel Charles Marsh Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, 1854-1899; Series II
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1870; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0726., 001072
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0728., 001074
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1867; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0731., 001077
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0732., 001078
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0733., 001079
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0734., 001080
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1887-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0742., 001088
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0743., 001089
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-18?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0747., 001093
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0748., 001094
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1868; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0749., 001095
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0754., 001100
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0756., 001102
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0758., 001104
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0760., 001106
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1892-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0765., 001111
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0766., 001112
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-1892; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0771., 001117
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0774., 001120
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0775., 001121
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0776., 001122
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1874-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0777., 001123
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0778., 001124
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1896-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0782., 001128
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0786., 001132
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0789., 001135
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1895-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0792., 001138
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0793., 001139
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0799., 001145
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0807., 001153
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0809., 001155
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0810., 001156
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0811., 001157
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0813., 001159
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0814., 001160
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0818., 001164
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0819., 001165
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0820., 001166
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0821., 001167
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0825., 001171
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0828., 001174
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1857-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0830., 001176
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1870; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0834., 001180
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0835., 001181
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1892-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0836., 001182
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0837., 001183
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0843., 001189
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0845., 001191
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0846., 001192
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1890-1891; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0847., 001193
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0853., 001199
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1865-187?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0855., 001201
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0856., 001202
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1880; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0859., 001205
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0863., 001209
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0864., 001210
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0865., 001211
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1870; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0867., 001213
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0868., 001214
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0869., 001215
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0873., 001219
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1896-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0876., 001222
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0877., 001223
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1886-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0879., 001225
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1879; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0881., 001227
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0883., 001229
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1872; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0884., 001230
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1860-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0890., 001236
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0892., 001238
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0895., 001241
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0896., 001242
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-1897, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0897., 001243
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0899., 001245
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0902., 001248
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0905; is this Sir James Hector (1834-1907) curator of Wellington museum?., 001251
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1967; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0909., 001255
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0910., 001256
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0911., 001257
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0916., 001262
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0919., 001265
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1886, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0920., 001266
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0923., 001269
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0924., 001270
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1889-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0928., 001274
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0932., 001278
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1892; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0934., 001280
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0938., 001284
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0939., 001285
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0940., 001286
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0943., 001289
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0946., 001292
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1891, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0950., 001296
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1891-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0960., 001306
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1892; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0962., 001308
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1814?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0963., 001309
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0964., 001310
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0967., 001313
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0969., 001315
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0972., 001318
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0973., 001319
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0974., 001320
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0975., 001321
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0985., 001331
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0986., 001332
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1880; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0987., 001333
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0989., 001335
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1865-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0990., 001336
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1880; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0992., 001338
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1001., 001347
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1002., 001348
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1864-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1004., 001350
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1005., 001351
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1014., 001360
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1018., 001364
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1021., 001367
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1885, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1022., 001368
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-1884; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1023., 001369
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1026., 001372
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1027., 001373
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1887, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1033., 001379
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1036., 001382
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1045., 001391
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1890-1891; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1046., 001392
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1891-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1049., 001395
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1881; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1050., 001396
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1051., 001397
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1887-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1054., 001400
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1895, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1058., 001404
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1059., 001405
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1873-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1061., 001407
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1871-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1064., 001410
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1065., 001411
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1887-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1066., 001412
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1894-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1071., 001417
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1072., 001418
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1888, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1074., 001420
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1075., 001421
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1076., 001422
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1079., 001425
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1083., 001429
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1884; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1084., 001430
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1089., 001435
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1092., 001438
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1093., 001439
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1869, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1094., 001440